

## DONI PUTRA PURBAWA, S.KOM., M.KOM.



1996/08/07



Indonesia



+62 878 1862 3001



doniputrapurbawa@gmail.com

### **ABOUT ME**

I was born in Sidoarjo, in August 1996. I received SPACE Program Scholarship Awardee for six months as Saga University (Japan). I have completed bachelor's degree in Computer Science from Brawijaya University, in 2019, and master's degree from Institut Teknologi Sepuluh Nopember (ITS) in 2022.

I have been working in an IT company for over five years and specialized on system architect, backend engineer also project manager. My research interests include the scalable and inteligent system, artificial intelligent and blockchain technology.

## **ACHIEVEMENTS**

- Saga University Scholarship
   SPACE Exchange Program (2017 2018)
- Djarum Foundation Scholarship
   Outstanding Student Program (2016 2017)

# RESEARCH / PROJECTS

- NFT Marketplace Website (Artwithme)
   https://art-with.me
- Seewing Online Course (日本手芸普及協会)
   https://jhia.academy
- Machine Learning & Deep Learning Book
   Playstore: https://s.id/playstore-book-ml-dl
   Amazon: https://s.id/amazon-book-ml-dl
- COVID-19 Detection Tools (Inose C-19)
   Data Scientist, Model Maker

# (7)

Github

https://github.com/doni404



LinkedIn Doni Putra Purbawa

https://www.linkedin.com/in/doniputrapurbawa/

#### **EDUCATIONS**

Institut Teknologi Sepuluh 2020 - 2022 Nopember University (ITS)

Computer Science / Informatics Engineering Cumlaude Master (GPA 4.0 on a 4.0 scale)

Brawijaya University

2014 - 2019

Computer Science / Informatics Engineering Cumlaude Bachelor (GPA 3.79 on a 4.0 scale)

## WORKING EXPERIENCES

#### Gloding, Inc.

(Tokyo, Japan - Malang Branch, Indonesia)

Backend Engineering Manager 2019 - Now

 System Architect using Amazon 2018 - 2019 Web Service (AWS)

 Server Administrator using Amazon Web Service (AWS)

Part Time Backend Developer 2017 - 2018

#### PT Hikari Solusindo Sukses

(Depok, West Java, Indonesia)

Data Scientist August - December 2021

# PT. Kereta Api Indonesia (Persero)

(Bandung, West Java, Indonesia)

Web Developer (Internship) 2017

# MGM Research Group

(Brawijaya University, Indonesia)

Student Employee 2016 - 2017